=As Promised=
(Adapted from "The Villain's Guide to Love",
a story on Zhihu Yanyan)
=Episode 20=
(Chiming Bells Beneath Radiant Skies)
This time,
all you have done well
in the disaster relief efforts.
Good.
- Thanks to Your Majesty's benevolence.
- And your wise governance.
Father.
There is a Miss Mu by Boqing's side
who was once
the top courtesan in the Capital,
renowned for both
her zither playing and dancing.
At such a celebratory banquet,
why not invite her
forward to perform for us?
Excellent.
Wonderful.
Boqing deserves the greatest credit
for the disaster relief effort.
You should toast him.
Boqing certainly deserves
this toast from a beauty.
You did well
with the disaster relief effort.
Thank you, Father.
Your Highness.
Are you all right?
Tingting.
Don't leave me.
This...
Your Highness.
- This is hardly appropriate here.
- Indeed.
That's right.
Boqing.
Could it be
that Miss Mu
is the woman you once mentioned to me,
the one who had won your heart?
Yes.
The woman I love
is Mu Tingting.
Father.
It's rare for Boqing
to give his heart to someone,
and Miss Mu
is both talented and beautiful.
She and Boqing are well suited.
Why not grant them your blessing
and issue an edict for their marriage?
It would make a fine match.
Boqing.
Do you truly wish to marry her?
I do.
Please grant us this marriage, Father.
Very well.
I grant your request.
Choose an auspicious day
for the wedding.
Thank you, Father.
Congratulations, Boqing.
- Congratulations, Your Highness.
- My congratulations, Your Highness.
Please, this way.
Careful.
Your Highness.
I think I twisted my ankle.
An imperial prince of noble birth
and the most
beautiful woman in the Capital.
They do make a fine match.
(No.)
(He clearly planned to send Mu Tingting)
(to the Crown Prince as an informant.)
(And on the day of the disaster relief,)
(he clearly seemed to
be regaining some of his memories.)
(Either way,)
(he shouldn't
be acting like this today.)
(Something)
(must have gone wrong.)
Crown Princess.
The designs for your wedding invitations
with the Crown Prince
have arrived.
Would you like
to choose one with His Highness?
All right.
(Wenhua Hall)
Once you've finished writing
the invitations for your guests,
get some rest.
All right.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Xiaoyuan.
I look forward
to the day you can call me your husband.
May that day come soon.
Your Highness, take a look at these.
(Invitation)
This ink
seems rather...
Forgive me, Your Highness.
What urgent business
do you have, Your Highness?
The Seventh Prince is resting
and is not receiving visitors.
Mu Tingting.
You did something to Zhao Boqing.
You were supposed to be a pawn
he recruited as part of his plan.
Your target should've
been the Crown Prince.
What exactly are you up to now?
So what if I did?
I started working for the Seventh Prince
for money and status in the first place.
Even I can see now
that the Crown Prince
is deeply in love with you.
Why would I still compete
with you for his favor?
With looks like mine,
why shouldn't I set my sights
on becoming a Princess Consort?
What exactly did you do?
Did you poison him
or use Gu on him?
Give me the antidote.
What antidote?
We're very happy together now,
and practically inseparable.
I don't care how many
wonderful memories
he had with you before.
Now,
they can only belong to me.
Your Highness.
I'd rather die
than leave the Seventh Prince.
Tingting.
He Xiaoyuan.
How dare you hurt her?
I didn't.
Your Highness.
She forced me to take poison.
She said if I refused to leave you,
she would kill me.
Your Highness.
Please conduct yourself properly.
My heart belongs only to Mu Tingting.
If she's harmed at all while here,
I'll make your entire clan
pay with their lives.
(His memories really have returned.)
(But they've also)
(been transferred to her.)
I once thought the greatest pain
was having you forget me.
Only now do I realize
what hurts even more
is seeing you carry the love we shared
and give it to someone else.
Your Highness.
The love Gu has taken hold.
Now the Seventh Prince
has eyes only for me.
Nothing is ever certain.
We mustn't let our guard down.
Zhao Boqing is strong-willed.
If he notices anything amiss,
the love Gu may begin to lose its hold.
Then what would you have me do?
He Xiaoyuan has
an awkward kind of vitality.
You need to learn from her.
Learn
her unguarded recklessness
and sincerity.
Your Highness.
I'm a dancer, not an actress.
I know how to charm a man,
but pretending to be foolish
is beyond me.
Then learn.
If you want to secure
your position as Princess Consort,
do as I say.
How am I supposed to learn that?
Who could possibly teach me?
I
will teach you myself.
Enough.
I really can't learn this.
Your Highness, with a figure
and a face like mine,
I was born to captivate men.
Why should I learn that awkwardness
unfit for polite company?
Awkwardness needs genuine affection
to be endearing,
while true charm takes only a glance.
You can't even maintain
that much composure.
Your Highness truly
is innocent and proper.
There's a reason you lost
to the Seventh Prince before
and failed to win a woman's heart.
Forget it.
I'll teach you.
A man who wants to charm a woman
doesn't need words.
You've been ordering me around
and lecturing me for so long.
Now it's my turn.
I'll teach you
how to win a woman's heart.
Suppose I'm the woman you desire.
I'll come over
and strike up a conversation.
Find some excuse
to touch me.
I don't like
touching women without good reason.
It wouldn't be without good reason.
Let your feelings guide you
and find a natural excuse.
Like this?
Not bad.
You're exceptionally
quick to learn, Your Highness.
Keep practicing.
Someday,
you'll surely win He Xiaoyuan's heart.
I'll be going, then.
♪My longing has nowhere to rest♪
♪Through the storm, I drift and sway♪
♪You are the prayer I hold in my palm♪
♪In one frozen moment,
my tears come into focus♪
♪My heart has long known♪
♪We made a promise long ago♪
♪To stay together until the end of time♪
♪You are the fate I cannot escape♪
♪How much must I let go♪
♪For one moment♪
♪To hold each other close♪
♪Would that be enough?♪